well it looks like our fearless lawyer did actually make an honest mistake so first off
the alarm went off in the cannon building which is the building where all the offices are not in
the capitol building which is where all the voting go down so even if this did happen it would not
have obstructed the actual vote happening in the capitol building this was the sign in front of
the door that he went through this sign don't make no sense emergency exit only push until
alarm sounds three seconds door will unlock in 30 seconds and apparently this sign was in a door
that he usually goes through that's not an emergency exit i still stand by that jamal bowman is a real
one wu-tang forever but it looks like in their efforts at this point to try and say that he did
this to obstruct justice and try to hold him accountable in a way that they did not want to
hold any of january 6th accountable looks like they're not going to be able to hold this one up
yeah yeah yeah so we fight on but i mean what i said you cannot win fighting fair with cheaters
and i stand on that